Finding Aid for the Dewey Daane Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- American Economic Review (Box 36)
  - Sep 1978, Dec 1978, Dec Supplement 1978 (Box 36)
  - Jun 1979, Sep 1979 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1980, Jun 1980, Sep 1980, Dec 1980 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1981, Jun 1981, Sep 1981, Dec 1981 (Box 36)
  - Mar 1982, Jun 1982, Sep 1982 (Box 36)
  - Sep 1986 (Box 36)
  - American Economic Review Directory of Members, Oct 1974 (Box 36)
- American Economic Review (Box 37)
  - Mar 1966, May 1966, Jun 1966, Sep 1966, Sep 1966 Part 2, Dec 1966 Mar 1967, May 1967, Jun 1967, Dec 1967 (Box 37)
  - May 1968, Jun 1968, Jun 1968 Part 2, Sep 1968, Dec 1968 (Box 37)
  - May 1969 (Box 37)
  - May 1974 (Box 37)
  - May 1975 (Box 37)
  - May 1976 (Box 37)
  - Feb 1977 (Box 37)
  - May 1979 (Box 37)
  - May 1980 (Box 37)
  - May 1981, Dec 1981 (Box 37)
  - May 1982 (Box 37)
  - May 1988 (Box 37)
- BIS-Bank for International Settlements- Recent Innovations (Box 38)
- International Banking –, April 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF 1966-1971-The System Under Stress Vol. 1:Narrative by Margaret Garritsen de Vries (Box 38)
- IMF 1966-1971-The System Under Stress Vol. 2:Documents by Margaret Garritsen de Vries (Box 38)
- IMF- World Economic and Financial Surveys- Primary Commodities, May 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Export Credits, July 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Staff Studies for the World Economic Outlook, July 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- International Capital Markets, Dec 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Recent Experience with Multilateral Official Debt Rescheduling, Feb 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 44- A Review of the Fiscal Impulse Measure, May 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 45- Switzerland’s Role as an International Finance Center, July 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 46- Fund- Supported Programs, Fiscal Policy, and Income Distribution, Sept 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 47 Aging and Social Expenditure in the Major Industrial Countries, 1980-2025- Sep 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 48 The European Monetary System: Recent Developments-, Dec 1986 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 52 Structural Reform, Stabilization and Growth in Turkey-, May 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 53 Floating Exchange Rates in Developing Countries-, May 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Occ. Papers 54- Protection and Liberalization: A Review of Analytical Issues-, Aug 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- World Economic and Financial Surveys- World Economic Outlook, Apr 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Primary Commodities, May 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Staff Studies for the World Economic Outlook, Aug 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- World Economic Outlook, Oct 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- World Economic Outlook Advance Copy, Oct 1987 (Box 38)
- IMF- Proposed Amendment to Articles of Agreement, Apr 1968 (Box 38)
- IMF- Proposed Second Amendment to the Articles of Agreement, Mar 1976 (Box 38)
- G-10 Communique of Ministers and Governors and Report of Deputies, Jul 1966 (Box 38)
- George H. Willis Speech-, Nov 7, 1967 (Box 38)
- National Advisory Council on International Monetary and Financial Policies- Special (Box 38)
  - Report to the President and Congress on Proposed Establishment of a Facility (Box 38)
  - Based on Special Drawing Right in the IMF and Modifications in the Rules on Practices of the Fund, Apr 1968 (Box 38)
- House of Representatives- Special Drawing Right-, May 6, 1968 (Box 38)
- IMF- The Role of the IMF in Today’s World Economy- J. DeLarosiere (Box 38)
- IMF- Economic Adjustment in Developing Countries and the Industrial Countries- J. DeLarosiere (Box 38)
- IMF- Restoring Fiscal Discipline, A vital Element for Economic Recovery- J. DeLarosiere (Box 38)
- IMF-Selected Decisions of the IMF and Selected Documents 9th Issue, Jun 15, 1981 (Box 38)
- IMF- Balance of Payments Adjustments, 1945-1986- The IMF Experience- Margaret Garritsen de Vries (Box 38)
- IMF- The IMF in a Changing World 1945-1985, Margaret Garritsen de Vries (Box 38)
- IMF- Articles of Agreement-, Feb 1973 (Box 38)
- IMF- Articles of Agreement-, Aug 1974 (Box 38)
- IMF- Articles of Agreement-, May 1982 (Box 38)
- IMF- Selected Decisions of the Executive Directors and Selected Documents Fifth Issue-, Jul 10, 1971 (Box 38)
- The World Bank’s Borrowing Program: Some Questions and Answers by Eugene H. Rotberg, Sep 1979 (Box 38)
- The Relationship Between the IMF and the World Bank- Joseph Gold from Creighton Law Review Vol. 15, 1981-1982, No 2- 1982 (Box 38)
- Co-Financing- Review of World Bank Co-Financing with Private Financial Institutions World Bank, Aug 1980 (Box 38)
- Adjustment and Financing in the Developing World- The Role of the IMF- Ed. by Tony Killick (Box 38)
- Institute for International Economics-Policy Analyses in International Economics- (Box 38)
  - - The Lending Policies of the IMF- John Williamson, 1-Aug 1982 (Box 38)
  - - International Debt and the Stability of the World Economy- William R. Cline, 4-Sep 1983 (Box 38)
  - - The Exchange Rate System- Jon Williamson, 5-Sep 1983 (Box 38)
  - - A New SDR Allocation?- John Williamson, 7-Mar 1984 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1963 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1967 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1968 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1969 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1974 (Box 38)
- IMF-Summary Proceedings- Annual Meeting-, 1981 (Box 38)
- IMF Pamphlet Series- (Box 38)
- No 12- The Reform of the Fund- Joseph Gold, 1969 (Box 38)
- No 13- Special Drawing Rights Character and Use- Joseph Gold, 1970 (Box 38)
- No 15- Special Drawing Rights Role of Language- Joseph Gold, 1971 (Box 38)
- No 20- Voting Majorities in the Fund: Effects of 2nd Amendment of Articles- Joseph Gold, 1977 (Box 38)
- No 25- The 2nd Amendment of the Fund’s Articles of Agreement- Joseph Gold, 1978 (Box 38)
- No 34- Compensatory Financing Facility- Louis M. Goreux-, 1980 (Box 38)
- No 36- SDRs, Currencies and Gold: Fifth Survey of New Legal Development- Jospeh Gold, 1981 (Box 38)
- No 37- The IMF: Its Evolution, Organization and Activities, 1984 (Box 38)
- No 38- Fund Conditionality: Evolution of Principles and Practices- Manuel Guitian, 1981 (Box 38)
- No 39- Order in International Finance, The Promotion of IMF Stand-by Agreements and Drafting of Private Loan Agreements- Joseph Gold, 1982 (Box 38)
- No 42- The IMF- Its Financial Organization and Activities- Anand G. Chandavarkar, 1984 (Box 38)
- Foreign Affairs- Vol. 68 No 1, 1988/1989 (Box 39)
- Foreign Affairs- Vol. 71 No 2 Spring, 1992 (Box 39)
- Foreign Affairs- Vol. 71 No 5 Winter, 1992/1993 (Box 39)
- Foreign Affairs- Vol. 72 No 1, 1992/1993 (Box 39)
- Setting National Priorities- Henry J. Aaron (Box 39)
- Setting Domestic Priorities: What Can Government Do?- Henry J. Aaron (Box 39)
- House of Representatives- Violent Crime Control and Law Enforcement Act of, 1994 (Box 39)
- The Australian Economy: A View from the North- Richard E. Caines and Lawrence B. Krause (Box 39)
- Economic Report of the President-, Feb 1994 (Box 39)
- Guide to the Federal Budget Fiscal 1988- Stanley E. Collender (Box 39)
- The Atlantic Community Quarterly- Summer 1984- Vol. 22 No 2 (Box 39)
- Setting National Priorities: The 1980 Budget- Joseph A. Pechman (Box 39)
- Setting National Priorities: The 1984 Budget- Joseph A. Pechman (Box 39)
- Setting National Priorities: The 1983 Budget- Joseph A. Pechman (Box 39)
- The Guide to the Federal Budget Fiscal 1989- Stanley E. Collender (Box 39)
- The Guide to the Federal Budget Fiscal 1990- Stanley E. Collender (Box 39)
- The Guide to the Federal Budget Fiscal 1991- Stanley E. Collender (Box 39)
- Conference Series No 24- The Future of the Thrift Industry-, Oct 1981 (Box 39)
- Owen Recruitment Book (four different years, no dates) (Box 39)
- Owen- Alumni Directory, 1990, 1991, 1992, 1993 (Box 39)
- VU Commencement Program, May 1987, May 1989, May 1990 (Box 39)
- Owen- Student Book- 1974-75, Fall 1975, Fall 1976, Fall 1977, Class of 1982, Class of 1983, Class of 1984, Class of, 1989 (Box 39)
- VU- Staff Handbook (no date) (Box 39)
- VU- Computing at Vanderbilt (no date) (Box 39)
- VU- The Registery-, Oct 1989, Nov 190 (Box 39)
- VU- Faculty Manual-, 1990-91, 1991-92, 1992-93, 1993 (Box 39)
- VU- Owen Bulletin-, 1975-76, Feb 1978, Dec 1978, Jan 1980, 1980-81, 1983-84, 1984-85, 1985-86, 1986-87, 1987-88, 1988-89, 1989/90, 1991-92, 1992-93 (Box 39)
- Owen- Directory-, 1978-79 through 1993-94 (Box 39)
- Report of the University Committee on Diversity-, Apr 1991 (Box 39)
- Owen- Walker Management Library- Collection Policy-, March 1988 (Box 39)
- Reducing the Deficit: Spending and Revenue Options March, 1994 (Box 40)
- A vision of Change for America, Feb 17, 1993 (Box 40)
- Reducing the Deficit: Spending and Revenue Options, Feb 1993 (Box 40)
- FRB of St. Louis- Review- Vol. 76 No 2 Mar/Apr 1994- Money Stock Measurement (Box 40)
- FRB of St. Louis- Review- Vol. 76 no 3, May/Jun 1994 (Box 40)
- Principles of Economics: Class Test Version Macroeconomics- David Colander (Box 40)
- Budget of the U.S. Government Fiscal Year, 1994 (Box 40)
- American New Beginning: A Program for Economic Recovery, Feb 18, 1981 (Box 40)
- The Need for International Reserves- George H. Willis and Fred L. Springborn- U.S. Treasury Dept., Sep 1967 (Box 40)
- Blueprints for Basic Tax Reform-, Jan 17, 1977 (Box 40)
- World Development and Report, 1978 (Box 40)
- Mitchell, Hutchins Inc- International Economic and Financial Profile Second Quarter, 1976 (Box 40)
- Export- Import Bank of the U.S.- Annual Report, 1975 (Box 40)
- The National Advisory Council on International Monetary and Fiscal Policies Annual Report to President and Congress, 1977 (Box 40)
- Toll of the Twin Deficits- CED (Box 40)
- CBO- Apr 1986- The Budgetary and Economic Effects of Oil Taxes (Box 40)
- CBO- Feb 1989- An Analysis of President Reagan’s Budgetary Proposal for FY, 1990 (Box 40)
- CBO- Mar 1990- The Federal Deficit: Doesn’t Measure the Government’s Effect on National Savings? (Box 40)
- World Bank- Annual Report, 1975 (Box 40)
- CED- International Economic Consequences of High-Priced Energy (Box 40)
- Economic Notes Vol. III No 3- Sep-Dec 1974- Monte Dei Paschi di Siena (Box 40)
- The Crisis in World Materials- A U.S.- Japanese Symposium-, Jun 1974 (Box 40)
- The 1989 Economic Report of the President-, Jan and Feb 1989 (Box 40)
- The 1989 Joint Economic Report- Congress-, May 1989 (Box 40)
- CSAB- International Challenges for American Banking-, Oct 1989 (Box 40)
- Frank M. Engle Lecture Apr 21, 1988- H. Robert Heller- Imbalances and Asymmetries in the World Economy (Box 40)
- Third World Debt and Global Recovery- 1983 Jodidi Lecture- The Center for International Affairs- Harvard University by A. W. Clausen, Feb 24, 1983 (Box 40)
- Restructuring the Thrift Industry: What Can We Learn from the British and Canadian Models?- Conf. At Lehigh University, Mar 1, 1989 (Box 40)
- OECD- Jan 1968 Catalog of Publications (Box 40)
- NYU- Grad School of Business Administration- Institute of Finance- Bulletin Nos., 91-92 (Box 40)
- Oct 1973 “Imported Inflation” and the Balance of Payments- Samuel I. Katz The U.S. Budget in Brief- Fiscal Year, 1990 (Box 40)
- Foreign Policy No 32 Fall, 1978 (Box 40)
- Binder- Letters from FRB of Richmond to College Classes in Economics and Banking Discussing the Practical Operations of the Fed. Res. System from, 1921-1926 (Box 41)
- Binder- Notes on Fed. Res. System-, 1914-1951 (Box 41)
- Binder- Part Three Fed. Res. Credit Policies- Original and Draft- Part IV Fed. Res. Credit Policies, 1925-1929 (Box 41)
- Managing the Dollar, Revised Draft- Sherman J. Maisel, Dec 1972 (Box 41)
- The U. S. in the Changing World Economy- Statistical Background Material- Peter G. Petersen, Dec 27, 1971 (Box 41)
- A Foreign Economic Perspective- Peter G. Petersen, Dec 27, 1971 (Box 41)
- Report to the Ad Hoc Subcommittee on Reserve Proposals, May 13, 1966 (Box 41)
- Relationships Between Changes in Member Bank Reserve Positions and Short-Term Interest Rates, Feb 1958 (Box 41)
- Relationships Between Changes in Member Bank Reserve Positions and Short-Term Interest Rates Feb 1958 Appendix A Qualitative Analysis (Box 41)
- Relationships Between Changes in Member Bank Reserve Positions and Short-Term Interest Rates Feb 1958 Appendix B Statistical Analysis (Box 41)
- The Money side of the “The Street”: Some Mechanic of the NY Money Market-Carl H. Madden, Jun 1958 (Box 41)
- Citibank- A Preliminary Report by the Nader Task Force on First National City Bank 1971- Intro by Ralph Nader- David Leinsdorf, Project Director (Box 41)
- Fed. Res. System- Staff Economics Studies- A Study of Factors affecting the Money Stock: Phase One Leonall C. Andersen (Box 41)
- Appendices C and D- “Rate Relationships in the Government Securities Market June 1952-1957 and Amount, Sources and Cost of Dealer Borrowings- Winfield W. Riefler (Box 41)
- Misc. Papers on International Finances [mostly Harvard Business School] (Box 41)
- U.S. Monetary Regulations and Its Instruments- Ralph A. Young, Apr 27, 1970 (Box 42)
- Evaluation of Regional Balance of Payments Analysis- Warren Smith (Box 42)
- Balance of Payments of the Southeast in 1950- Gloria J. Hile (Box 42)
- Binder- FRB- Listing of Individual Bank info 1973/74, Retiree Reunion info 1980 and Professional Research Personal in the FRS-, Jan 1974 (Box 42)
- Binder- A Symposium on Money, Interest Rates and Econ. Activity- Apr 6, 1967- ABA (Box 42)
- Binder- Harvard Business School- Capital Markets- Andrew F, Brimmer Spring Semester 1975- Handouts (Box 42)
- Binder- Research Dept Forms [Harvard Business School Handouts] (Box 42)
- Binder- Advanced Planning Commission- Description of the Long Range Financial (Box 42)
- Environment Apr 23, 1971 William W. Sherrill (Box 42)
- Binder- LRIPC Agenda-Summaries-Notes, 1962, 1963 (Box 42)
- Binder- LRIPC Agenda-Summaries-Notes 1964, 1965, 1966- List of all LRIPC (Box 42)
- Documents issued by Treasury (Box 42)
- Binder- International Economic Developments- Basle, Apr 8-9, 1974 (Box 42)
- Binder- BIS Book Jan 1973 (Book Prepared for Chairman’s Trip) (Box 42)
- Extra Handout from Seminar in Monetary and Fiscal Policy, 1989 (Box 43)
- -Monetary Policy and Open Market Operations During, 1987 (Box 43)
- -Fed. Res. Policy and Interest Rates: Analysis and Predictions- David M. Jones, Mar 29, 1989 (Box 43)
- -M1 M2 M3 Graphs (Box 43)
- -The Economics and the Morality of the Budget Deficit- Rudolph G. Penner (Box 43)
- -Challenge to Leadership, Ed. by Isabel V. Sawhill- Chapter 9 Fiscal Choices by Joseph J. Minarik and Rudolph G. Penner (Box 43)
- -Is Money Irrelevant? Gerald P. Dwyer, Jr. and R. W. Hafer (Box 43)
- -Chicago Fed Letter Jan 1989 No 17 (Box 43)
- -Economic Perspectives Jan/Feb 1989- FRB Chicago (Box 43)
- Debt Defying Feats of U.S. Corporations (Box 43)
- Dealing with Budget Deficit- Rudolph G. Penner (Box 43)
- -CED- Part 1: Intro and Overview to Policy Implications of Demographic Change by R. Scott Fosler (Box 43)
- CED- Social Security and National Savings- Rudolph G. Penner (Box 43)
- Philosophy and Properties of the DRI Model of the U.S. Economy-Roger E. Brinner (Box 43)
- -Fed. Res. Press Release- Feb 9, 1990 (Fed Open Market Commission) (Box 43)
- -Alan Greenspan Feb 20, 1990- Subcommittee on Domestic Monetary Policy (Box 43)
- -Monetary Policy Report to Congress Pursuant to the Full Employment and Balanced Growth Act of 1978-, Feb 20, 1990 (Box 43)
- -FRB of San Francisco – Weekly Letter Mar2, 1990- Price Level Stability (Box 43)
- -American Economic Review Vol. LVIII No 1 Mar 1968- The Role of Monetary Policy- Milton Friedman (Box 43)
- -Recent Tech. of Monetary Policy-Henry C. Wallich Economic Review, May 1984 (Box 43)
- -Significance of Rational Expectations Theory- Bennett T. McCallum – Challenge, Jan/Feb 1980 (Box 43)
- -Monetary Policy, Money Supply and the Federal Reserve’s Operating Procedures- Stephen H. Axilrod- Fed. Res. Bulletin, Jan 1982 (Box 43)
- -U.S. Monetary Policy in Recent Years: An Overview- Stephen H. Axilrod Fed. Res. Bulletin, Jun 1985 (Box 43)
- IMF- Annual Reports, 1980-1990 (Box 43)
- IMF- Annual Reports, 1960-1963 (Box 43)
- IMF- By-Laws Rule of Regulations- 31st Issue, Apr 30, 1973 (Box 43)
- IMF- Summary Proceedings Annual Meeting, 1964-1966 (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Economic Choices 1984- Alice M. Rivlin, Ed. (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Economic Choices 1987- Henry Aaron et al (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Brookings Papers on Economic Activities 1, 1979 (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Brookings Papers on Economic Activities 1, 1980 (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Brookings Papers on Economic Activities 2, 1980 (Box 43)
- Brookings Institute- Brookings Papers on Economic Activities 1, 1981 (Box 43)
- IMF- O.P. 1- International Capital Market- Recent Developments and Short-Term Prospects R. C. Williams, Sep 1980 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 2- Economic Stabilization and Growth in Portugal- Hans O. Schmitt, Apr 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 3- External Indebtedness of Developing Countries- Bahran Mowzad and Richard C. Williams, May 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 4- World Economic Outlook: A Survey by the Staff of the IMF, June 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P.5- Trade Policy Developments in Industrial Countries, July 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 6- The Multilateral System of Payments: Keynes, Convertability and the IMF’s Articles of Agreement- Joseph Gold, Aug 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 7- International Capital Markets: Recent Developments and Short-Term Payments, 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 8- Taxation in Sub-Saharan Africa, Oct 1981 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 9- World Economic, Outlook 1982 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 19- The European Monetary System: The Experience, 1979-82-May 1983 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 21- World Economic, Outlook 1983 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 27- World Economic, Outlook 1984 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 42- The Global Effects of Fund-Supported Adjustment Programs, May 1986 (Box 44)
- IMF- O.P. 43- International Capital Markets-Development and Prospects, Feb 1986 (Box 44)
- IMF- World Economic Outlook-, May 1980, Apr 1985, Apr 1986, Apr 1989, May 1990, May 1991, May 1993, Oct 1993, May 1994 (Box 44)
- IMF- Issues and Developments in International Trade Policy, Aug 1992 (Box 44)
- IMF- Official Financing for Developing Countries, Apr 1994 (Box 44)
- IMF- Private Market Financing for Developing Counties, Dec 1992, Dec 1993 (Box 44)
- IMF- Staff Studies for World Economic Outlook, Dec 1993 (Box 44)
- Book- Robert Solomon, the International Monetary System 1945-1981 [4 copies] (Box 44)
- Foreign Affairs- America and the World 1992/1993 Vol. 72 No 1 (Box 44)
- Foreign Affairs- Summer 1993 Vol. 72 No 3 (Box 44)
- AEI- Contemporary Economic Problems- William Fellner, Project Director, 1978 (Box 44)
- AEI- Contemporary Economic Problems- William Fellner, Project Director, 1979 (Box 44)
- AEI- Contemporary Economic Problems- William Fellner, Project Director, 1980 (Box 44)
- AEI- Essays on Contemporary Economic Problems: Demand, Productivity, and 1981-1982 Edition, William Fellner Project Director (Box 44)
- AEI- A Study in Contemporary Economic Problems- Politics Versus Markets: International Differences in Macroeconomic Policies- Stanley W. Black-, 1982 (Box 44)
- AEI- A Study in Contemporary Economic Problems- The High-Employment Budget and the Potential Output: A Critique Focusing on Two Recent Contributors- William Fellner, 1982 (Box 44)
- AEI- Essays on Contemporary Economic Problems, 1982 William Fellner (Box 44)
- The U.S. Role in a Changing World Political Economy: Major Issues for the 96 th Congress- A Compendium of Papers, Jun 25, 1979 (Box 44)
- Inflation and the Income Tax- Henry J. Aaron, Editor- Brookings Institute (Box 44)
- Book- The New Economic Role of the American States: Strategies in a Competitive World Economy- R. Scott Fosler, 1988 (Box 44)
- BIS- Bank for International Settlements- Annual Report, 1988/89, 1989/90, 1990/91, 1991/92 (Box 45)
- DRI- The Data Resources- Review of the U.S. Economy-, Jun 1982 (Box 45)
- Banking and Payment Systems International Conf.-Papers and Comments, Apr 2-4, 1980 (Box 45)
- U.S. Dept of Commerce- U.S. Income and Output, Nov 1958 (Box 45)
- IMF- External Debt in Perspective-, 1983 (Box 45)
- The U.S. in the Changing World Economy- Peter G. Petersen, Dec 27, 1971 (Box 45)
- U.S. Monetary Policy: Its Contribution to Prosperity Without Inflation, the American Assembly Columbia University, Oct 16-19, 1958 (Box 45)
- Book- The Econometrics of Price Determination- Conf., Oct 30-31, 1970- D.C. (Box 45)
- The President’s 1978 Tax Program- Dept of Treasury (Box 45)
- The President’s 1978 Tax Program- Detailed Descriptions and Supporting Analyses of the Proposals-Dept of Treasury (Box 45)
- The National Banking Review- Sep 1963 Vol. 1 No 1 (Box 45)
- The National Banking Review- Jun 1965 Vol. 2 No 4 (Box 45)
- The National Banking Review- Sep 1965 Vol. 3 No 1 (Box 45)
- The National Banking Review- Dec 1965 Vol. 3 No 2 (Box 45)
- CED- Strengthening the Federal Budget Process: A Requirement for Effective Fiscal Control (Box 45)
- Payment Systems in Eleven Developing Countries- BIS (Box 45)
- Public Policy and Capital Formation- Fed. Res. System (Box 45)
- Years of Reform- A Prelude to Progress- 101st Annual Report 1963 Comptroller of the Currency (Box 45)
- Arthur Anderson and Co.- VAT in other Countries: An Arthur Anderson Co. Study 1979 (Box 45)
- The Potential for Conflict in National Politics and In Financial Markets- Henry Kaufman (Box 45)
- Federal Revenue Sharing- A New Appraisal- Tax Foundation Inc. 1969 (Box 45)
- Recommendations for Change in the U.S. Financial System, Sep24, 1973 (Box 45)
- The Potential Competition Doctrine- Assn. of Registered Bank Holding Co. (Box 45)
- Staff Economic Studies- Imported Inflation and the International Adjustment Process- Ruth Logue- Federal Reserve System (Box 45)
- Economic Expansion, Deficits and Interest Rates- Henry Kaufman (Box 45)
- Inflation? What’s That? Five Essays on Inflation- Dr. George W. McKinney, Jr.- Irving Trust (Box 45)
- International Reserves and Liquidity-A Study by the Staff of the IMF (Box 45)
- Economic Priorities in the 1970’s- Paul W. McCracken (Box 45)
- Employment and Unemployment: Priorities for the Next Five Years (Box 45)
- To Lower Interest Rtes- The Credit Allocation Act of 1975- Hearing – Committee on Banking, Currency, and Housing-, Feb 19, 1975 (Box 45)
- CBO- Reducing the Federal Budget: Strategies and Examples-, Feb 1980 (Box 45)
- CBO- Advance Budgeting: A Report to the Congress-, Feb 24, 1977 (Box 45)
- CBO- Establishing a Multiyear Budget Framework-, Dec 9, 1977 (Box 45)
- Congressional Budget Reform- Senate Budget Committee, Aug 1976 (Box 45)
- 5 Memorandum on Carter H. Golembe Associates, Inc. Letterhead (Box 45)
- International Institute for Economic Research- Midnight Economist: Broadcast Essays XI- William R. Allen-, Jan 1986 (Box 45)
- Marquis- Who’s Who in America 37th Edition 1972-73 Vol. 1 A-K and Vol. 2 L-Z (Box 46)
- Proposed 2nd Amendment to the Articles of Agreement of the IMF- Mar 1976 [3 copies] (Box 46)
- Binder- Data on International Developments- Prepared by Division of International Finance-, 1973 (Box 46)
- CSAB- U.S. Productive Capacity: Estimating the Utilization Gap, Dec 1977 (Box 46)
- CSAB- Substitution of a Federal Value-Added Tax for the Corporate Income Tax: An Equilibrium Analysis- Robert Defina, Oct 1979 (Box 46)
- CSAB- Alternative Policies to Combat Inflation-, Jan 1979 (Box 46)
- Business Focus- Fall 1986-Publication of the Center for the Study of American Business CBO- List of Publications- Spring, 1978 (Box 46)
- CBO- Understanding Fiscal Policy-, Apr 1978 (Box 46)
- Economic Stabilization Policies: The Historical Record 1962-1976- House Budget Committee, Nov 1978 (Box 46)
- CBO- Income Policies in the U.S.: Historical Review and Some Issues, May 1977 (Box 46)
- CBO- International Balance of Payments Financing and the Budget Process CBO- Interpreting Early Warnings of Inflation, Aug 1977 (Box 46)